The U.S. State Department issued a level 3 travel advisory for Jamaica,
urging Americans to exercise increased caution due to an increase in the violent crime dem.
Incidents such as home invasions, armed robberies, sexual assault, and homicide
are common in the country, and sexual assaults are frequent, including at all-inclusive resorts.
News Nation travel editor Peter Greenberg said,
The good news is, in most cases, these crimes are not crimes committed or targeted at travelers or tourists.
They be thinking they're saying something when they say things like this.
Like, he's literally like, the good thing is that this is only happening to the local blacks.
This is not happening to people.
Wow.
That's essentially what he's saying.
I feel like it's really wild that Jamaica is getting travel advisories,
but, like, America is not issuing travel advisories.
If you go into D.C. or to Bay, here's a travel advisory.
Don't drive.
If you're in Atlanta, and this goes for the Bay as well, and you do have to drive,
don't leave nothing in that car.
Leave the windows down.
Now, if you're going to Detroit, you know, I don't know what to tell you, okay?
Just careful on the east side.
They are always going to give you reasons not to leave this place.
That's American exceptionalism, and it's BS.
And when you do travel, you see white people everywhere enjoying themselves.
You should be there, too.
Get your passport.